export const QuestionsInputMap = [

    // British Questions Map Custom // 

    {
        question: "Which Country Was Never a Formal Part of The British Empire?",
        choice1: "Sudan",
        choice2: "Belize",
        choice3: "Afghanistan",
        choice4: "South Africa",
        answer: "Afghanistan",
        
    },
               
    {
        question: "What is the First Colony of the British Empire?",
        choice1: "Wales",
        choice2: "North American Colonies",
        choice3: "Scotland",
        choice4: "Ireland",
        answer: "Ireland",
    },
   
    {
        question: "Who is the Black Prince?",
        choice1: "Henry I",
        choice2: "Henry IV",
        choice3: "Edward III",
        choice4: "Edward of Woodstock",
        answer: "Edward of Woodstock",
       
    },
       
    {
        question: "Who is the Longest Regining British Monarch?",
        choice1: "Alfred the Great",
        choice2: "Cnut the Great",
        choice3: "Elizabeth II",
        choice4: "Elizabeth I",
        answer: "Elizabeth II",
       
    },
       
    {
        question: "When Did the British Empire End?",
        choice1: "1967",
        choice2: "1978",
        choice3: "1801",
        choice4: "1997",
        answer: "1997",
       
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Jewel in the British Empire's Crown? - Territory",
        choice1: "Canada",
        choice2: "The 13 Colonies",
        choice3: "India",
        choice4: "Austraila",
        answer: "India",
       
    },
    {
        question: "The British Empire Reached its Greatest Extent in...",
        choice1: "1914",
        choice2: "1800",
        choice3: "1930",
        choice4: "1999",
        answer: "1930",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the British Prime Minster During World War Two?",
        choice1: "Lord Dudley",
        choice2: "Winston Churchill",
        choice3: "Lord Hailfax",
        choice4: "Andrew Jackson",
        answer: "Winston Churchill",
        
    }, {
        question: "During Which War did English Kings conquer large areas of France?",
        choice1: "The Crusades",
        choice2: "World War Two",
        choice3: "The Norman Conquest",
        choice4: "The Hundred Years' War",
        answer: "The Hundred Years' War",
        
    }, {
        question: "In the 1700s, the English Were at War with?",
        choice1: "Spain",
        choice2: "France",
        choice3: "India Princedoms",
        choice4: "All of the Above",
        answer: "All of the Above",
        
    }, {
        question: "Which Country's Colonies were given to Great Britain by the Treaty of Versailes in 1919?",
        choice1: "Spain",
        choice2: "France",
        choice3: "Germany",
        choice4: "The Netherlands",
        answer: "Germany",
        
    }, {
        question: "The English became the Dominant Power in India after which Battle?",
        choice1: "Battle of Crete",
        choice2: "Battle of Plassey",
        choice3: "Battle of Waterloo",
        choice4: "None of the Above",
        answer: "Battle of Plassey",
        
    }, {
        question: "How Many Overseas Territories remain under British Sovereignty?",
        choice1: "None",
        choice2: "Three",
        choice3: "Fourteen",
        choice4: "Six",
        answer: "Fourteen",
        
    },
    {
        question: "The Great Game Refers to the Cold War Style Conflict between Great Britain and...?",
        choice1: "Russia",
        choice2: "France",
        choice3: "Germany",
        choice4: "The United States",
        answer: "Russia",
        
    },
    {
        question: "The British Empire Relied Primarily on Its ... Power to Defend itself",
        choice1: "Naval",
        choice2: "Army",
        choice3: "Industrial Might",
        choice4: "The English Spirit",
        answer: "Naval",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Which General Defeated Napoleon the I at the End of the Napoleonic Wars?",
        choice1: "William III",
        choice2: "The Duke of Wellington",
        choice3: "Charles II",
        choice4: "The Duke of Hanover",
        answer: "The Duke of Wellington",
        
    },
    {
        question: "Women Were Fully Allowed to Vote in Great Britain in____?",
        choice1: "1914",
        choice2: "1925",
        choice3: "1903",
        choice4: "1928",
        answer: "1928",
        
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Square Root of X-2?",
        choice1: "HELL if I Know!",
        choice2: "Lol Math",
        choice3: "I'm a Nerd",
        choice4: "Math is Great!",
        answer: "HELL if I Know!"
        
    },
];